Hahaha.
What?
Hey, Jigs.
I haven't seen you since.
Hey, yo.
No, I feel it's all right.
Oh, I don't think so.
Hi, ma!
Hi, God.
Part of you wants to be mad at her for kidnapping us,.
but you got to love her energy.
Where are my matters?
Chop chop gentlemen look alive.
Perfection you know I was so delighted that you accepted my invitation here tonight.
Well thrown us in a burlap sack wasn't exactly an e-bike.
Vic you're so quiet. Oh you feel I'm sad cat got your tongue would you prefer a new noose?
Excuse me. How do you two know each other let me handle this junior? Oh, don't junior me you may call me Garfield Mr. Garfield or G money.
Okay, whatever no G money anyway can somebody please tell me what is going on?
Oh really I'll take this one.